[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Delinquents, released in 1957, was Robert Altmans first feature film. How long did it take to film it in Kansas City?", "correct_answer": "two weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["two months", "nine months", "half a year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Nazi from the movie Shindlers List was ranked #15 on the American Film Institutions list of the top movie villains?", "correct_answer": "Amon Goeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Adolph Hitler", "Wilhelm List", "Josef Gobbels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We all hate spam on our computers. What is the computer term for sending spam as an instant messenger message?", "correct_answer": "Spim", "incorrect_answers": ["Inspam", "Spamage", "InstaSpam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Excluding map supplements and special editions, how many issues of The National Geographic Magazine are published each year?", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["52", "36", "24"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did Eve of Destruction hit the screen?", "correct_answer": "1991", "incorrect_answers": ["1998", "1984", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of medical problems are shiitake mushrooms beneficial for according to various studies?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tumor", "Immune system deficiency", "Thrombosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much could a full-grown Smilodon weigh?", "correct_answer": "450 lbs.", "incorrect_answers": ["525 lbs.", "350 lbs.", "400 lbs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the 2006 album Stadium Arcadium by the Red Hot Chili Peppers, which song is about the death of  bassist Fleas dog?", "correct_answer": "Death of a Martian", "incorrect_answers": ["Wet Sand", "Tell Me Baby", "Dani California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Frank Gorshin plays the Joker in the 1960s Batman TV series.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By act of Congress, this is the official alcoholic spirit of the USA.", "correct_answer": "Bourbon", "incorrect_answers": ["Corn liquor", "Gin", "Rye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1967 comedy, which may be the Top Ten American movie with the lowest profile and one of the lowest budgets, starred a newcomer named Dustin Hoffman.", "correct_answer": "The Graduate", "incorrect_answers": ["Kramer Vs. Kramer", "Tootsie", "Marathon Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Perfect Storm, who are the two crew members who jump in the water to save Murphs life when he is pulled overboard by a line that gets hooked through his hand?", "correct_answer": "Sully and Bobby", "incorrect_answers": ["Bugsy and Sully", "Bobby and Billy", "Billy and Alfred Peirre"]}]